//   ---------------------------------------subraction questions--------------------------
const level8SubQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "what is 97 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "90", "92", "89"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 50 - 8?",
        "options": ["42", "43", "45", "49"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 84 - 8?",
        "options": ["76", "77", "79", "83"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 71 - 8?",
        "options": ["63", "64", "66", "70"],
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 13 - 8?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "10", "12"],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 60 - 8?",
        "options": ["52", "53", "55", "59"],
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 99 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "92", "94", "98"],
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 48 - 8?",
        "options": ["40", "41", "43", "47"],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 76 - 8?",
        "options": ["68", "69", "71", "75"],
        "answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 18 - 8?",
        "options": ["10", "11", "13", "17"],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 90 - 8?",
        "options": ["82", "83", "85", "89"],
        "answer": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 33 - 8?",
        "options": ["25", "26", "30", "32"],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 65 - 8?",
        "options": ["57", "58", "60", "64"],
        "answer": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 10 - 8?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "5", "9"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 84 - 8?",
        "options": ["76", "77", "79", "83"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 29 - 8?",
        "options": ["21", "22", "24", "28"],
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 51 - 8?",
        "options": ["43", "44", "46", "50"],
        "answer": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 8?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 21 - 8?",
        "options": ["13", "14", "16", "20"],
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 45 - 8?",
        "options": ["37", "38", "40", "44"],
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 72 - 8?",
        "options": ["64", "65", "67", "71"],
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 6 - 8?",
        "options": ["-2", "-1", "0", "4"],
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 83 - 8?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "80", "82"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 94 - 8?",
        "options": ["86", "87", "89", "93"],
        "answer": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 50 - 8?",
        "options": ["42", "43", "45", "49"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 8?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 10 - 8?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "5", "9"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 97 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "90", "92", "89"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 29 - 8?",
        "options": ["21", "22", "24", "28"],
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 72 - 8?",
        "options": ["64", "65", "67", "71"],
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 6 - 8?",
        "options": ["-2", "-1", "0", "4"],
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 83 - 8?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "80", "82"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 94 - 8?",
        "options": ["86", "87", "89", "93"],
        "answer": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 45 - 8?",
        "options": ["37", "38", "40", "44"],
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 21 - 8?",
        "options": ["13", "14", "16", "20"],
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 8?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 83 - 8?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "80", "82"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 97 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "90", "92", "89"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 50 - 8?",
        "options": ["42", "43", "45", "49"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 84 - 8?",
        "options": ["76", "77", "79", "83"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 71 - 8?",
        "options": ["63", "64", "66", "70"],
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 13 - 8?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "10", "12"],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 60 - 8?",
        "options": ["52", "53", "55", "59"],
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 99 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "92", "94", "98"],
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 48 - 8?",
        "options": ["40", "41", "43", "47"],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 76 - 8?",
        "options": ["68", "69", "71", "75"],
        "answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 18 - 8?",
        "options": ["10", "11", "13", "17"],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 90 - 8?",
        "options": ["82", "83", "85", "89"],
        "answer": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 33 - 8?",
        "options": ["25", "26", "30", "32"],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 65 - 8?",
        "options": ["57", "58", "60", "64"],
        "answer": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 10 - 8?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "5", "9"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 84 - 8?",
        "options": ["76", "77", "79", "83"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 29 - 8?",
        "options": ["21", "22", "24", "28"],
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 51 - 8?",
        "options": ["43", "44", "46", "50"],
        "answer": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 8?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 21 - 8?",
        "options": ["13", "14", "16", "20"],
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 45 - 8?",
        "options": ["37", "38", "40", "44"],
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 72 - 8?",
        "options": ["64", "65", "67", "71"],
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 6 - 8?",
        "options": ["-2", "-1", "0", "4"],
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 83 - 8?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "80", "82"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 94 - 8?",
        "options": ["86", "87", "89", "93"],
        "answer": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 50 - 8?",
        "options": ["42", "43", "45", "49"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 8?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 10 - 8?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "5", "9"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 97 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "90", "92", "89"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    
    
    {
        "question": "what is 29 - 8?",
        "options": ["21", "22", "24", "28"],
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 72 - 8?",
        "options": ["64", "65", "67", "71"],
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 6 - 8?",
        "options": ["-2", "-1", "0", "4"],
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 83 - 8?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "80", "82"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 94 - 8?",
        "options": ["86", "87", "89", "93"],
        "answer": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 45 - 8?",
        "options": ["37", "38", "40", "44"],
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 21 - 8?",
        "options": ["13", "14", "16", "20"],
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 8?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "73", "77"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 83 - 8?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "80", "82"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 97 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "90", "92", "89"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 50 - 8?",
        "options": ["42", "43", "45", "49"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 84 - 8?",
        "options": ["76", "77", "79", "83"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 8?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "33", "37"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 71 - 8?",
        "options": ["63", "64", "66", "70"],
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 13 - 8?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "10", "12"],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 60 - 8?",
        "options": ["52", "53", "55", "59"],
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 99 - 8?",
        "options": ["91", "92", "94", "98"],
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 8?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "19", "23"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 48 - 8?",
        "options": ["40", "41", "43", "47"],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 76 - 8?",
        "options": ["68", "69", "71", "75"],
        "answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 18 - 8?",
        "options": ["10", "11", "13", "17"],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 57 - 8?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "52", "56"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 90 - 8?",
        "options": ["82", "83", "85", "89"],
        "answer": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 33 - 8?",
        "options": ["25", "26", "30", "32"],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 65 - 8?",
        "options": ["57", "58", "60", "64"],
        "answer": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 10 - 8?",
        "options": ["2", "3", "5", "9"],
        "answer": "2"
    }
      ];
      function shuffleArray(array) {
        for (let i = array.length - 1; i > 0; i--) {
          const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i + 1));
          [array[i], array[j]] = [array[j], array[i]];
        }
        return array;
      }
      
      level8SubQuestions.forEach(question => {
        question.options = shuffleArray(question.options);
      });
    
    export default level8SubQuestions;